<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Plugin>
  <Name>UGREEN iDX6011 Pro Front Panel</Name>
  <PluginURL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/noodlemctwoodle/unraid-ugreen-idx6011-pro/main/ugreen-idx6011-pro.plg</PluginURL>
  <PluginAuthor>noodlemctwoodle</PluginAuthor>
  <Support>https://github.com/noodlemctwoodle/unraid-ugreen-idx6011-pro/issues</Support>
  <Project>https://github.com/noodlemctwoodle/unraid-ugreen-idx6011-pro</Project>
  <ReadMe>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/noodlemctwoodle/unraid-ugreen-idx6011-pro/main/README.md</ReadMe>
  <Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/noodlemctwoodle/unraid-ugreen-idx6011-pro/main/images/ugreen-idx6011-pro.png</Icon>
  <Category>Tools:System</Category>
  <Beta>False</Beta>
  <Date>2026-07-13</Date>
  <Overview>
Fully customisable touch LCD dashboard + smart front-panel LEDs and fan control for the
UGREEN NASync iDX6011 Pro, running natively on Unraid - no UGOS required. Build your own
dashboard pages from a module library, drive the fans, and theme everything from the
Unraid web UI. Model-gated via DMI, so it safely no-ops on other hardware.
  </Overview>
  <Description>
Touch LCD dashboard + smart front-panel LEDs for the **UGREEN NASync iDX6011 Pro**,
running natively on Unraid - no UGOS required.

- **Customisable dashboard** on the 258x960 front touchscreen: build any page from a
  library of modules (CPU, memory, network, storage, GPU, NPU, power, fans, uptime,
  array status, OS/plugin updates, docker, VMs, and per-item disk / interface /
  container / VM cards), each with a choice of visual styles - bar, ring, gauge, history
  graph, area, blocks, split, trend or big number.
- **Web Layout editor** with a live preview: add / rename / reorder / delete pages, pick
  each module's style, and theme the font, sizes and full colour palette. Point at any
  image on the server for the **wallpaper / header logo** (hot-swaps live, no restart),
  make cards translucent, hide the header / title / page-dots for a **full-screen image
  page**, add spacer gaps, and save / load / share **theme presets**.
- **Fan control**: drive all four chassis fans on temperature curves (Auto / Silent /
  Quiet / Turbo) or Max, with a never-stall floor - live RPM and an animated spinning-fan card.
- **Smart front LEDs** (power / 2x LAN / 6x disk): configurable colours, SMART health
  (green/amber/red), LAN link, and an activity mode that blinks on I/O.
- Self-contained: downloads a SHA256-verified payload and registers its own EFI boot
  entry (no UGOS/NVMe/grub dependency). Model-gated via DMI - no-ops on other hardware.

Requires the BIOS Watchdog Timer disabled and the panel EFI entry set first in the BIOS
boot order. See the project README before installing.
  </Description>
  <Changes>
###2026.07.13
- Fully customisable dashboard with a module library and many visual styles; web Layout
  editor with a live preview; panel-driven four-fan curve control (Auto/Silent/Quiet/
  Turbo/Max) with an animated Fans card; theming (font, sizes, full palette incl. card-title
  and dim colours, network units); richer stats (docker container IPs + update flags, VMs,
  NPU, fans); smarter configurable front LEDs; and a redesigned settings UI.
- Wallpapers and themes: point at any image on the server for the wallpaper / header logo
  (hot-swapped live, no restart); translucent cards (global or per-page opacity), spacer
  gaps, and per-page full-screen image pages (hide header / title / dots); plus theme
  presets you can save, load and share as files.
- Power-save schedule: turn the screen and disk/LAN LEDs off between two local times
  (quiet hours); a tap wakes everything and it re-sleeps 30s after the last touch. The
  timezone comes from Unraid automatically.
###2026.07.12.1
- New plugin icon.
###2026.07.12
- Initial release. The full front panel for the UGREEN NASync iDX6011 Pro on Unraid.
  </Changes>
</Plugin>
